lanka-ads.com 2018-06-13

# Privacy Policy | Lanka ads

This is The Lanka Ads's Privacy Policy. BPO Lanka ("We" or “Us” or “Our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our Terms and Conditions of Use and any other documents referred to on it) explains how we collect, use and handle any personal information we collect from you when you use our website at [lanka-ads.com (our "Lanka Ads"). We understand your disclosure of personal information is a serious matter. So, the protection and appropriate use of your personal information is important to us

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting the Site you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the **Act** ), the data controller is Lanka Ads.

**Collecting your personal information**

We may collect and process the following data from:

**Information you give us**. You may give us information about you or relating to you:

  * if you register to become a user of Lanka Ads;
  * if you send us a message from Lanka Ads or correspond with us by telephone in writing or otherwise;
  * as you visit web pages on Lanka Ads;
  * if you subscribe to one of our services;
  * participate in a discussion board or other social media functions on Lanka Ads;
  * If you enter a competition, promotion or survey;
  * If you report a problem to us; and
  * from any of your activities in connection with your use of Lanka Ads.

Before you can access and use all of Lanka Ads’s features and services, you must register to become a user of Lanka Ads.

To register, we ask that you provide us with certain personal information, which will generally include your name, address, phone number, email address, date of birth, academic record, profile picture and personal website (each to allow Us to customise your experience), a username and a password created by you. You may also elect to upload materials to your profile that include personal information.

**Information We collect about you.** With regard to each of your visits to Lanka Ads we may automatically collect the following information:

  * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
  * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call Our customer service number.

**Information We receive from other sources.** We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. [In this case We will have informed you when We collected that data that it may be shared internally and combined with data collected on this site.] We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.

**How We use your personal information**

We use your personal information to create and maintain your user account and profile for Lanka Ads and to provide you with the services We offer through Lanka Ads.

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, We may use personal information to:

  * send you information about your account, the services we or our related companies provide or any changes or upgrades that We make to those services;
  * to alert you of relevant opportunities and activities (including, without limitation, jobs, workspaces, content and notifications (for example, if another user is following your profile));
  * to send you newsletters which you may either elect to receive or may be interested in given your user account and/or profile; and/or
  * to provide you with any other information or services you request that We provide.

Except as set out in this Privacy Policy or otherwise agreed by you, We will not share your personal information with third parties (such as marketing companies) or use your personal information other than for Our internal purposes.

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

**Sending messages from Lanka Ads**

We may provide 'support' links on Lanka Ads that enable you to send emails directly to Us (for example, if you need assistance with any of our services or generally in relation to Lanka Ads). We will retain emails you send for the purposes of contacting you and for Our internal purposes.

**Cookies**

We uses 'cookies' to identify information about your web browser session and personalisation data each time you visit Lanka Ads. A 'cookie' is a small data file that will be stored by your web browser when you access Lanka Ads. These cookies do not contain any of your personal information such as name or email, the information stored in the cookie will only identify you to Lanka Ads. Cookies can be used to enhance your use of Lanka Ads, as We use them to help personalise Our delivery of services and material to you, such as information which is most relevant to your profile and interests.

You can set up your browser so that it does not accept Our cookies. You can also manually delete Our cookies from your browser. However, you will not be able to login to Lanka Ads without cookies being enabled on your browser. When browsing without logging in, some features may not behave as intended when cookies are not accepted.

**How we may share your information**

We may engage third parties to undertake some of Lanka Ads's services or related services such as hosting, archiving, data security and email communications. We may provide those third parties access to personal information for the sole purpose of them providing their services to Us. We will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that those third parties only use your personal information for the specific purposes for which it is provided to them and consistently with this Privacy Policy.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * to analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of Lanka Ads;
  * to Our related companies;
  * to Our professional advisors;
  * to law enforcement authorities, if We suspect that an unlawful act is being committed or that such disclosure will prevent that unlawful act; or
  * as otherwise required or authorised by law.

If you apply for a position that is advertised via Lanka Ads, We will provide your contact details to the person or company advertising that position.

Similarly, if you have been sent a "handshake" from another user of Lanka Ads to get in contact with them, We will facilitate them to contact you via Lanka Ads and display certain details about your availability (if you have filled that information), however, your personal information is not shared with them.

Other than the types of disclosures set out in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise agreed by you, We will not disclose your personal information to any third party.

**Security of your personal information**

We will use reasonable security measures to protect your personal information from loss or unauthorised access, use or disclosure.

**Your access to your personal information**

You are entitled to know what personal information We hold about you. You are also entitled to update or correct your personal information. If you would like to contact us in relation to your personal information, please do so by email to [help@lanka-ads.com](mailto:help@lanka-ads.com). Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet Our costs in providing you with details of the information We hold on you.

**Third party websites**

Please be aware that Lanka Ads may contain links to third party websites. If you visit such websites, before providing your personal information on or in connection with those websites, We suggest you review the privacy policy and terms and conditions of use of the third party website.

**Changes to Our privacy policy**

Any changes We may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or change to Our privacy policy.

**Contact**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [help@lanka-ads.com](mailto:help@lanka-ads.com).
